import 'package:sample_quiz_app/view/questions.dart';

const List<QuestionModel> questions = [
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    question: "Programming lang used in flutter",
    options: [
      "a. C++ ",
      "b. Dart ",
      "c. Android ",
      "d. Node js",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    question: "Flutter is a : -",
    options: [
      "a. Programming language ",
      "b. Software ",
      "c. Framework ",
      "d. Website",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    question: "which of these is not a datatype in dart?",
    options: [
      "a. const ",
      "b. int ",
      "c. bool ",
      "d. var",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    question: "which is not an OOPs sub concept here?",
    options: [
      "a. Getter ",
      "b. abstract ",
      "c. Class ",
      "d.  Overloading",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    question: "full Form of OOP",
    options: [
      "a. Organized Object Program ",
      "b. Object Oriented Programming ",
      "c. Object Organized Programming ",
      "d.  Objective Oriented Progrmming ",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    question: "How many Widgets are there in Flutter",
    options: [
      "a. 3 ",
      "b. 4 ",
      "c. 2 ",
      "d.  5",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    question: "Flutter used to build application for?",
    options: [
      "a. Android ",
      "b. Java ",
      "c. IOS ",
      "d.  both a & c",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    question: "which of these are not a state management tool?",
    options: [
      "a. getX ",
      "b. bloc ",
      "c. Sqflite ",
      "d.  Provider",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    question: "which of these are not a mode in flutter?",
    options: [
      "a. Profile mode ",
      "b. Reload mode ",
      "c.  Debug mode ",
      "d.  Release mode",
    ],
  ),
  QuestionModel(
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    question: "how many modes are in flutter?",
    options: [
      "a. 2 ",
      "b. 4 ",
      "c. 3 ",
      "d.  5",
    ],
  ),
];
